I'm feeling pretty tired.
ひょうそと疲れ気味ですね
Do you like your job?
仕事がいいですかね?
Are you a pervert?
変態でしょ?
I'm not an unreasonable person.
無理者じゃないですかもん
hey.
ね
Please follow me closely.
も っとついてください
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
You came again.
また来てくれたんですね
I'm feeling pretty tired.
ひょうそと疲れ気味ですね
sorry.
すみません
Didn't you hate it this time?
今回は嫌じゃなかったですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Can I have it removed?
外してもらっていいですか?
Remove the microphone.
マイクを外す
You can remove the mic.
マイクを外せるんですね
Do you like your job?
仕事がいいですかね?
Service
仕
Things are good.
事 がいい
It's a little naughty after all.
やっぱりちょっとエッチなの
I have a job.
仕事が
Can I have you take it off?
脱いでもらっていいですか?
Are you a pervert?
変態でしょ?
I like that outfit.
いいね、その服
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's cute, kind of.
かわいいね、なんか
This is so amazing
めっちゃこれ、
Isn't it a foldable book?
折 りまんじゃないですかも
Hmm.
ん ね
It looks white.
白に見えますね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
My pants are going to stretch.
伸びちゃうね、パンツが
not at all.
全然
Everyone feels good like this.
みんな、こういう、みんなの気持ちがいいよね
That's not true.
そんなことない